cvp.com 2013-12-19

# CVP website security and privacy policy

Website security and privacy policy

We take your security and privacy very seriously. This document details the information about you that we collect,  how we use it and the steps we take to ensure that it is kept secure. If you have any questions about this privacy policy or the security of this website please contact us.

By using this web site you consent to us collecting and using personal information about you as specified in this policy. We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please check back here regularly.

|   
---|---  
|   | 

**Server security**

Any information we hold is 128-bit encrypted and stored on our own dedicated server which is scanned daily and certified secure & CPI compliant by McAfee SECURE™.  

The McAfee SECURE™ standard is an aggregate of industry best practices, designed to provide a level of security that an online merchant can reasonably achieve to help provide consumers with better protection when interacting with websites and shopping online.

All data stored is in compliance with current data protection act legislation.

**Cookies**

**We use a cookie so that we can recognise you when you visit our website and track your activity whilst on our website. The cookie only remains on your computer if you elect to store it in the user information page. The cookie we store on your computer only contains a unique reference number so that we can link you to your account with us. No personal information is contained within the cookie itself.**

**The information we collect**

We store the information you supply when becoming a member of www.cvp.com and / or placing an order online, however we do not store your credit card information.  We do collect and store Information related to your visits to this site (such as which pages you visit, how often you visit).  All information collected is encrypted and stored securely.

Use of stored information

We use gathered information to help us improve our web site. We will also use your information to keep you informed of special offers, money off promotions, products or services that we think might interest you. We do not share your information with third parties.  
  
---|---|---  
  
By supplying us with your information you confirm that you do not consider use of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy to be a breach of any of your rights under the Telecommunications (Data Protection and Privacy) Regulations 1999.

You should be aware that if we are requested by the police or any regulatory or government authority investigating suspected illegal activities to provide your personal details and / or information concerning your activities whilst visiting this site, we shall do so.

Thank you for taking the time to read our privacy policy.
